[
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "A client's Chiropractor wants your progress notes on the client. What do you do?",
    "options": {
      "a": "give them directly to the chiropractor",
      "b": "don't give them at all",
      "c": "get client's consent before releasing the notes c. get client's consent before releasing the notes"
    },
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "Which is a common endangerment site?",
    "options": {
      "a": "sternal notch",
      "b": "calcaneous",
      "c": "patella"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "During the refractory period, which of the following is true?",
    "options": {
      "a": "impulses are firing constantly",
      "b": "impulses can be sent through the neuron",
      "c": "impulses cannot be sent through the neuron c. impulses cannot be sent through the neuron"
    },
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "A client has Migraines. Which meridians should you work?",
    "options": {
      "a": "LR/GB",
      "b": "ST/SP",
      "c": "BL/KI"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "Which of these muscles is the easiest to palpate?",
    "options": {
      "a": "tibialis anterior",
      "b": "tibialis posterior",
      "c": "plantaris",
      "d": "flexor digitorum longus"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "Which organ opens to the tip of the tongue?",
    "options": {
      "a": "HT",
      "b": "ST",
      "c": "SP",
      "d": "LU"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "Yin is best described as which?",
    "options": {
      "a": "hollow and dorsal",
      "b": "scattered",
      "c": "solid and ventral"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "solid and ventral"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "Which organ/meridian would be indicated with Eczema and Asthma?",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Lung"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": "For which condition would passive ROM not be effective or indicated?",
    "options": {
      "a": "piriformis syndrome",
      "b": "simple sprain",
      "c": "tendonitis",
      "d": "acute rheumatoid arthritis rheumatoid arthritis"
    },
    "correct_option": "d",
    "correct_answer_text": "acute rheumatoid arthritis"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "A client has been diagnosed with whiplash in the last 24 hours (the injury happened then) an MD has prescribed massage. How would you work on them?",
    "options": {
      "a": "work the anterior neck with friction and ice",
      "b": "start the treatment with traction",
      "c": "wait until the acute phase is over before beginning neck work - beginning neck work"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "wait until the acute phase is over before beginning neck work -"
  }
]